Clearbit Privacy Policy
=======================

**Clearbit Privacy Policy**

Last updated: February 13, 2024

This Privacy Policy describes how we process, handle, or otherwise maintain data we collect, including in connection with your use of our products, services, APIs, apps, and websites that link to this policy (we refer to these collectively as our "Services").

Clearbit is committed to protecting and processing your personal information responsibly. We value the data you share with us and treat it with respect.

**Welcome to Clearbit! So, Who Are We?**

API Hub, Inc. dba Clearbit is a Delaware corporation and HubSpot Affiliate, with a registered office at 548 Market St. #95879, San Francisco, CA 94104 ("Clearbit," "we," "us," etc.). To contact us, see the "Contact Us!" section below.

Clearbit, a B2B Marketing Intelligence tool, provides go-to-market teams with a comprehensive B2B dataset across company, contact, and IP address intelligence. By using our full dataset, customers are able to enrich key systems, build products, and power personalization.

Our Services are designed to help our customers and partners in a wide variety of ways, including by helping them determine which companies might make the best customers, identify the contacts within those organizations by department, role, or seniority to improve or expedite their interactions with those companies, and enabling them to personalize their interactions with those companies.

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect or maintain, including through our website ("Site"), software (including APIs, browser extensions, and integrations with third-party software) and other Services.

**This Privacy Policy includes additional notices that may apply to you if you live in certain jurisdictions, such as residents of the European Economic Area, United Kingdom, Brazil, or California.** These notices may include information on how to exercise certain rights you may have with respect to personal information. Please see the section below titled "Additional Notices for Specific Jurisdictions" for more details.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of any companies we don't control, including the privacy practices of our customers. For example, our customers may obtain information from Clearbit about business contacts or prospects. We do not control their use and disclosure of this information. In certain circumstances, we act as a processor or service provider on behalf of our customers, and in those circumstances, it is the customer that is responsible for the processing of your personal information. For clarity, if we process personal information under an agreement in which Clearbit acts as a processor or service provider to a customer, that agreement governs the processing of your personal information and not this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns with the privacy practices of our customers or other third parties, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of those entities.

**The Information We Collect**

We collect information in the following ways: (1) information you provide directly to us, (2) information we collect through our Services (3) information we collect through the use of technologies such as cookies, and (4) information we collect from third parties, including through Clearbit Indexers.

**Information you provide directly to us**

Your Interactions with Us:

When you browse or visit our Site, contact us, install our free products or set up a user account with us, we might collect information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as through a web form, in an email or other message (including in the "envelope" of the message, such as the From: or Subject: lines), or during the account creation process. The information we or our vendors collect directly from you may include:

* **Identifiers** , such as your name, business address, email address, and similar identifiers;
* **Transaction Information** , such as the Services you've purchased or considered purchasing, and similar commercial information;
* **Professional or Employment-Related Information** , such as your job title and/or roles within your employer;
* **Financial Information** , such as credit card or other banking information, billing name, and billing address, if you purchase Services from us;
* **Support Service Information** , such as messages submitted to us through email or customer support, and summaries or voice recordings of interactions with our customer service personnel;
* **Other Information You Provide** , such as if you provide feedback, comments, or other information through communications with us.

In accordance with applicable laws, we may record any calls, training sessions, webinars, or similar events that you participate in with us.

**Information We Obtain When Customers Use Our Services**

We may collect information when our customers use our analytics-based, data-driven solutions in their business-to-business marketing and sales efforts. We may receive personal information about your online activity and commercial information based on your interactions with our customers. This could include sales data, website activity data, and business contact and lead information.

When our customers use certain Services, Clearbit may receive data from the website visitors of those customers. Some of the data we receive may be considered personal information, such as IP address, cookie identifiers, and other identifiers that are automatically assigned to your computer or devices when you access the Internet.

**Information from cookies, web server logs, and other technologies**

Like many other commercial websites, we may also automatically gather information in connection with your use of the Site or Services through the use of "cookies" and other similar technologies such as web server logs, pixels, and end-user website activity (collectively, "Tracking Technologies"), including the Clearbit tag. Information gathered through Tracking Technologies may include internet or other electronic network activity information, such as IP addresses, identifiers derived from email addresses for the purposes of cross-device tracking for targeted advertising, the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, links to/from any page, and time spent at a site. For more information about how we use Tracking Technologies when you visit our Site or other online services, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://clearbit.com/cookie-policy).

We use third-party analytics services, such as Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Services. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://clearbit.com/www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can opt out of Google's collection and processing of the data your use of the services generates by going to [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Information from Third Parties**

Publicly Available Information:

We or our service providers may collect publicly available information about businesses and the personnel who work or were previously employed with them. Such information could include identifiers, such as name, title, company or business, business contact information, email address, employment history, social media data, and similar information.

Third Parties:

Third parties, including certain data vendors and our customers, may provide us with information through licensing, sponsorship, or other agreements. For example, we provide certain services to customers in which customers authorize us to collect certain information and data to develop professional profiles ("Business Profile Information") that are compiled into our commercial database. We also obtain information from third-party providers, partners and integrators who gather data from a variety of sources including data co-ops or publicly available sources. Such information could include identifiers, such as name, title, department company name, company's officers, and certain company employees, business and/or cell phone numbers, fax number, office address, email addresses, employment and education history, social media data, and similar information.

In addition, we may collect information from third parties such as customers, web-based and mobile networks, exchanges, aggregators, and publishers that is collected from their sites and properties, which might include identifiers such as IP address, cookie and other unique identifiers that might be considered personal information. The type of information collected via the identifiers might include information about online behavior, such as pages visited, time spent on a web page, session start/stop time, whether the visitor scrolled through or clicked on an ad or webpage, and referring website address, that is then associated with the company identified.

**Clearbit Indexers**

Our proprietary indexing systems ("Clearbit Indexers") collect information from a variety of sources in order to compile "Attribute Data" about corporations, non-profits, and similar entities ("Companies") and the professionals that work for them ("Professionals"). A complete list of Attribute Data we make available to users of the Site and Services can be found at [www.clearbit.com/attributes](https://clearbit.com/attributes).

Our Clearbit Indexers collect a variety of information and data for purposes of creating our database of Attribute Data and for providing, improving, and maintaining the Services. We collect personal information as Attribute Data, and to help us compile, organize, and verify Attribute Data, in the following ways:

(1) from publicly accessible sources, both online and offline, algorithmically through the Clearbit Indexers or provided by third parties;

(2) through licensing agreements directly with data brokers or other Companies; and

(3) directly contributed by individuals about both Professionals and Companies, except where such information is provided pursuant to an agreement in which Clearbit acts as a processor or service provider.

We use Attribute Data to provide the Services, for internal research and development purposes, and to maintain and improve the quality of our Services. We may also use Attribute Data to collect metadata, such as activity signals or IP registration information. We use this metadata to improve the quality of the Clearbit Indexers, and to verify the accuracy, integrity, and completeness of our Attribute Data.

Our Services are designed to help our customers and partners in a wide variety of ways, including by helping them determine which Companies might make the best customers, identify the contacts within those organizations by department, role or seniority that might improve or expedite their interactions with those Companies, and enabling them to personalize their interactions with those Companies.

**Clearbit Connect**

If you install Clearbit Connect, you make certain information and data available to us. For example, we will collect information about your web history and other electronic network activity information, such as IP address, in order to provide enriched company data based on the websites you visit. If you choose to use the Gmail integration with Clearbit Connect, you will be asked to give us access to certain information from your Gmail or Google account, including your name, email address, and Google profile information.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We may use the information we collect in the following ways:

* We may use Business Profile Information to provide enriched data to our customers and partners for their business-to-business marketing and sales purposes and for such business purposes as permitted under our agreements.
* For our operational purposes, such as responding to your inquiries, routing you to the Clearbit team member who can assist you, maintaining and servicing your account with us, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling your orders and transactions with us, verifying your information, processing payments, internal business functions such as accounting and forecasting, and similar purposes.
* For auditing, security, debugging, internal research and development, maintaining the quality and safety of our Services, and service performance purposes.
* To maintain, improve, and enhance the functionality and quality of our Site and other Services.
* To communicate with you about your accounts and activities involving us and our services, including changes to our Site and services.
* To enforce the legal terms that govern use of our Services, including to identify, prevent, and stop possible fraudulent activity.
* To comply with regulatory requirements.
* To provide the services you have requested.
* To better understand the sources of traffic and transactions on our Site.
* To personalize your experience and customize the Services.
* For internal research and development purposes.

We may de-identify information we collect so the information cannot reasonably identify you or your device, or we may collect information that is already in de-identified form. Our use and disclosure of de-identified information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may use and disclose it to others for any purpose, without limitation.

**Disclosures and Transfers**

We may disclose information in the following situations.

**With Customers**

We disclose information, such as [Attribute Data](https://clearbit.com/attributes), to our customers who may use this data for their internal sales and marketing operations, or in certain cases and with our permission, use it as part of their in-product offering.

We may also disclose Business Profile Information we collect and process for our customers to our other customers. Our customers' privacy policies discuss how they will use this information.

**Service Providers and Similar Third Parties**

We also disclose information with service providers and third parties for our operational purposes and other business purposes. Among other things, our service providers may provide web hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure (such as cloud computing), customer service, email delivery, security and other auditing, and similar services.

**Third-Party Advertising**

We also participate in some digital advertising networks ("Ad Networks") with which we disclose certain information collected through cookies and other Tracking Technologies, as well as analytics about the information we disclose to the Ad Networks. Ad Networks place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags). They also use these technologies, along with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you use, such as a mobile phone and a laptop. If you would like more information about this practice, and to learn how to opt out of it in desktop and mobile browsers on the particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, please visit [http://optout.aboutads.info/#/](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#/). You may download the AppChoices app at [www.aboutads.info/appchoices](http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices) to opt out in mobile apps.

**Governments, Law Enforcement, and Other Legal Requirements**

We may disclose information about you to law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties if we believe in our sole discretion that it is absolutely necessary or appropriate in order to (i) respond to a subpoena, court order, or other binding legal process; (ii) comply with laws, statutes, rules, or regulations, including without limitation those designed to protect your privacy rights; (iii) prevent physical or other harm, financial loss, or infringement of your rights, Clearbit's rights, or the rights of anyone else; or (iv) report suspected illegal activity or investigate and pursue violations of our binding contractual agreements.

In addition, we may disclose personal information as necessary in the event of a contemplated or actual merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or similar event for purposes consistent with that transaction. Note that, in such an event, information in our possession may be transferred to our successor or assign.

**Business Partners**

We may disclose personal information to our business partners and affiliates to fulfill our contractual commitments, or to provide you with a product or service that you have requested. We also disclose this information for marketing or sales purposes including in connection with conferences or events where (if applicable) you have consented to disclosure. We may also provide personal information to business partners we work with to jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you.

**Related Companies and Affiliates**

We may disclose your information to affiliates within the corporate group for our operational purposes and other business purposes. Our affiliates include our parent company, HubSpot. Inc, and any other affiliates, subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other HubSpot companies that we control or that are under common control with us either now or in the future.

**Your Data Rights**

**You have certain choices about your personal information. If you have questions or concerns regarding Clearbit's collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, or if you wish to exercise your rights, including the right to be removed from our Database, please complete** [**this form**](https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy) **, contact us at** [**privacy@clearbit.com**](mailto:privacy@clearbit.com) **or use any of the other methods described below. Where you have provided opt-in consent to the use of your personal information, we will also give you the option to opt out in a similar manner, as required by law.**

**Please note also that we may process information about you in some instances where we are acting as a data processor or service provider on behalf of other businesses. In such cases, we recommend that you contact the businesses to which you originally provided your personal information to complete the requests described below.**

**Opt Out of Cookies and Other Similar Technologies.** Your browser or device can allow you to opt out of data collection through cookies or similar technologies. Please note that your experience using the Site or the Services might be degraded, or certain functionalities may not work, if you opt-out to such collection. Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://clearbit.com/cookie-policy) for more information.

**Opt Out of Marketing Communications.** If you wish to opt out of our use of your contact information for our email marketing purposes, you can click the "Unsubscribe" button located within the most recent marketing email you received from us or submit your request at [https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy](https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy).

**Additional Rights.** Depending on where you are located, you may have additional rights. If you have any questions about whether these additional apply to you, please view the section titled "Additional Notices for Certain Jurisdictions" below. When exercising such rights, we may ask you to provide us with information necessary to reasonably verify your identity before responding to your request. We will consider all requests and provide our response within the time period required by applicable law. Please note, however, that certain information may be exempt from such requests. If we deny your request in whole or in part, you may have the right to appeal the decision. In such circumstances, we will provide you with information regarding the appeals process.

**EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework.** Clearbit complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Clearbit has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal information received from the European Union and the United Kingdom in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Clearbit has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal information received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the DPF Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

For personal information received under the Data Privacy Framework, Clearbit will require third parties to whom we disclose personal information to safeguard that personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy, obligating those third parties to provide at least the same level of protection as is required by the DPF Principles. EU, UK and Swiss citizens may choose to opt-out of such disclosures. Clearbit remains liable to individuals in case of such third parties' failure to comply with the DPF Principles or this Privacy Policy in handling onward transfer of such individuals' information, unless we can prove we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

EU, UK, and Swiss individuals have the right to request access to their personal information that we process under the Data Privacy Framework or request that we correct, amend, or delete their personal information if it is inaccurate or processed in violation of the DPF Principles. You may also opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. If you would like to exercise these rights, please write to us via contact details provided below.

In compliance with the Data Privacy Framework, Clearbit commits to resolving complaints about privacy and its collection or use of your personal information. EU, UK, or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Clearbit at privacy@clearbit.com. We will attempt to resolve any DPF-related complaints within forty-five (45) days of receipt.

Clearbit further has committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the DPF Principles to JAMS (Judicial Arbitration & Mediation Services), an independent alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and recognized for this purpose by the US Department of Commerce. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution) for more information, and to file a complaint. If neither Clearbit nor our alternative dispute resolution provider are able to resolve your complaint, you may pursue binding arbitration through the Data Privacy Framework Panel. For further information, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/How-to-Submit-a-Complaint-Relating-to-a-Participating-Organization-s-Compliance-with-the-DPF-Principles-dpf](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/How-to-Submit-a-Complaint-Relating-to-a-Participating-Organization-s-Compliance-with-the-DPF-Principles-dpf).

The Federal Trade Commission has enforcement authority regarding Clearbit's compliance with the DPF Principles.

**International Transfers**

Clearbit is based in the United States. Your personal information may be collected, transferred to, stored and otherwise processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Site and/or Services you acknowledge that your personal information may be transferred to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country and where data may be accessible to law enforcement and national security authorities under certain circumstances.

When we transfer personal information outside the EEA, UK, or Switzerland to a country that does not provide an adequate level of protection, we use a variety of legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer, including the European Commission-approved Data Privacy Framework, the EU Standard Contractual Clauses, as well as additional safeguards where appropriate. For transfers to or from the United Kingdom, we make use of the UK Addendum. Please contact us at [privacy@clearbit.com](mailto:privacy@clearbit.com) if you need more information about the legal mechanisms we rely on to transfer personal information outside the EEA, UK, and Switzerland.

**Additional Notices for Certain Jurisdictions**

You may be entitled to additional privacy notices depending on where you are located. Please see the appropriate subsection below that may apply to you.

**California**

Clearbit has prepared additional disclosures and notices for California consumers. Those additional disclosures can be found [here](https://clearbit.com/ccpa).

**Nevada**

If you would like to request that we refrain from selling your Covered Information (as defined under Nevada law), please submit your request at [https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy](https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy).

**Notice of Privacy Practices for Other U.S. States**

For disclosures required by the Colorado Privacy Act (CPA) regarding the categories of personal information, processing purposes, and information regarding personal information that we sell, please see the Information We Collect section of the Clearbit CCPA Policy, which can be found [**here**](https://clearbit.com/ccpa). Please note that the term "share" is defined differently in the CCPA and the CPA; we do not share personal information with third parties, as those terms are used in the CPA.

Applicable state law (such as the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act, Colorado Privacy Act, and the Connecticut Data Privacy Act) may give you certain rights. The law of your jurisdiction may permit you to request that we:

* Confirm whether or not we are processing your personal information and provide you with access such personal information;
* Correct inaccuracies in your personal information, taking into account the nature of the personal information and the purposes of the processing of the personal information;
* Delete your personal information;
* Provide you a copy of personal information that you previously provided to us in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format that allows you to transmit the data to another business, where our processing is carried out by automated means; and
* Opt you out of the processing of the personal information for purposes of targeted advertising, the sale of personal information, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects concerning you.

Certain information may be exempt from such requests under applicable law. We need certain types of information so that we can provide our Services. If you ask us to delete it, you may no longer be able to access or use the Services.

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please submit a request at privacy@clearbit.com or visit [https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy](https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy). You will be required to verify your identity before we fulfill your request. To do so, you will need to provide the information identified in the webform (including at a minimum your name and email address) or as otherwise directed by us.

Clearbit may sell your personal information or use your personal information to send you targeted advertising. To opt out of such sales and targeted advertising, please visit this link: [**Do Not Sell Or Share My Personal Information**](https://clearbit.com/ccpa-opt-out).

If we deny your request to exercise any of the rights above, you may appeal that denial by contacting us in the manner described below and describing in detail why you believe the denial was in error. Your description must include your full name and email address, along with a copy of the denial notice you received from us.

**Additional Disclosures for Individuals Outside the United States**

**Controller Status**

For EU, UK, and Swiss individuals, API Hub, Inc. dba Clearbit, a Delaware corporation with its registered office at 548 Market St. #95879, San Francisco CA 94104, is the controller of your personal information.

**Lawful Basis for Processing**

**The laws in some jurisdictions require companies to tell you about the legal ground they rely on to use or disclose your information. To the extent those laws apply, our legal grounds are as follows:**

* **Consent** : Where you have given consent to such processing for one or more specific purposes.
* **Contractual Obligation** : Where the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you.
* **Legal Obligation** : Where processing is necessary for compliance with our legal obligation.
* **Legitimate Interest** : Where processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of our customers (e.g. making available Business Profile Information to our customers (us), direct marketing and sales activities (our customers)), and your interests and fundamental rights and freedoms do not override those interests.

**Your Data Subject Rights**

**The laws of your jurisdiction may give you the right to:** be informed, access, rectify, or erase any personal information we have collected about you. You also have the right to data portability and the right to restrict or object to our processing of personal information we have collected about you. In addition, you have the right to ask us not to process your personal information (or provide it to third parties to process) for marketing purposes or purposes materially different than for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. You may withdraw your consent at any time for any data processing we do based on consent you have provided to us. If you choose to withdraw your consent, this will not impact the lawfulness of the data processing carried out up to that point.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us as set out below and specify which right you are seeking to exercise. We will respond to your request in accordance with applicable law. Please note that certain information may be exempt from such requests in some circumstances, which may include needing to continue processing your information for our legitimate interests or to comply with a legal obligation. We may require specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request, including, at a minimum, your name and email address. If personal information about you has been processed by us as a processor on behalf of our customer and you wish to exercise any rights you have with such personal information, please inquire with our customer directly.

If you have any issues with our compliance, you may contact us at [privacy@clearbit.com](mailto:privacy@clearbit.com). You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction. However, we encourage you to contact us first, and we will do our very best to resolve your concern.

**Protection and Retention of Information**

Clearbit considers the security of all the information and data within our control to be a top priority, and consistent with this we implement technical and organizational safeguards to protect from accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure of, or access to, such information or data. However, no security system is impenetrable, and unanticipated system failures or the efforts of malicious actors are an unfortunate reality on the internet. Therefore, we cannot guarantee that the information and data within our control, including personal information, is absolutely secure.

Clearbit retains the information described in this Privacy Policy for as long as is necessary to comply with legal obligations, enforce our agreements, maintain existing relationships with our customers, and otherwise as might be necessary for our legitimate business interests.

**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**

Your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a Do Not Track signal to websites and other online services you visit. We do not currently recognize or respond to browser-initiated Do Not Track signals. To find out more about Do Not Track, please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). Please note that Do Not Track is a different privacy mechanism than the Global Privacy Control browser choice referenced in our[Clearbit CCPA Policy](https://clearbit.com/ccpa).

**Our Policy Towards Children**

Clearbit provides business services, and as such we do not direct our services towards individuals under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 18. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from individuals under the age of 18, we take steps to delete that information in accordance with applicable law. If you become aware that Clearbit has improperly collected information from individuals under the age of 18, please contact us immediately at [privacy@clearbit.com](mailto:privacy@clearbit.com).

**Updates**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you, as appropriate, depending on the substance of the change, by email or by means of a notice on our website's homepage.

**Contact us!**

If you wish to ask us any questions about this Privacy Policy, or to exercise any of your rights described in this Privacy Policy, we can be reached in the following ways:

* To exercise your rights, please use Clearbit's Privacy Request form to submit a request to the privacy team. The Privacy Request form is available at [https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy](https://preferences.clearbit.com/privacy).
* Our toll-free phone number for privacy inquiries is (866) 241-4820.
* You can also email us at [privacy@clearbit.com](mailto:privacy@clearbit.com).
* You can reach us at 548 Market St #95879 San Francisco, CA 94104-5401. If you write to us, please address it to our Privacy Team.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

**Privacy Policy Archive**

* * *

[Trust Center](https://clearbitjs.com/trust)[Privacy Policy](https://clearbitjs.com/privacy-policy)[Status](https://clearbit.statuspage.io/)[Support](https://clearbitjs.com/support)[Legal](https://clearbitjs.com/legal)[Do Not Sell My Info](https://clearbitjs.com/ccpa-opt-out)Manage Cookies

© 2024 Clearbit
